= kisskh.lv =
♪ From primal chaos to the starry sky ♪
♪ In the whole world, we shall hold the balance ♪
♪ The cauldron tempers divine blades ♪
♪ The furnace refines the empty void ♪
♪ The Way is in mystic fate ♪
♪ Be brave enough to split the primal chaos wide open ♪
[Pull Strings]
[Adapted from the novel by Yan Gui Zheng Zhuan]
What did you smell?
I smell Changgeng the Great is here.
I must have him as my Mentor.
Found it.
I still don't know Changgeng's
true appearance,
but as long as he is here,
the Pregenesis Sword
must be here too.
Elder Kuai Si,
it's time to act.
Mentor, what are you doing?
Always so jumpy.
What's wrong?
Is that how you talk to your Mentor?
Show some respect.
Mind your tone with your disciple.
Next time you speak to your Mentor,
watch it a little.
Stop fidgeting.
What's wrong?
There's a mosquito.
It wasn't this dark earlier.
You kidding me?
So dark in here.
Hi.
[Episode 19]
[Hall of Mystic Truth]
What are you screaming for?
What's going on?
Possession?
Help! Run!
Hanzhi, go.
Mentor.
Pearl Elites, form up.
Run.
Xiong Da.
She's up there.
Lingli, run.
It hurts so much.
Stay back.
No, don't bite me.
No.
Don't bite.
Ascendance disciples, fall back.
Can't bite through?
Beat it.
Why doesn't it hurt?
You even bit my crotch.
So shameless.
Brothers, they eat people.
[Hall of Mystic Truth]
It's really solid.
Impressive.
Who?
3,000 spirit stones.
You Seizing Sect evildoer.
Still trying to trick Ascendance Sect?
Get out!
Just you wait.
What?
What's happening out there?
Xuanya, get inside.
Brat, what's going on?
It's nothing.
I heard the sounds of fighting.
Let me see.
It's the Demon Clan. A sneak attack.
A sneak attack?
Don't worry, Yunxiao.
Everything is going as planned.
Just...
It came sooner than I expected.
What about my fellow cultivators?
Go away.
They are safe with Zhao Gongming.
Rest assured, Yunxiao.
Uncle, run.
What are you doing?
Senior is in there. I must save her.
Calm down.
You can't save her on your own.
Remember what I told you about hearts?
Hearts?
Even the strongest man is futile alone.
Only a leader can save everyone.
What should I do?
Don't catch me. Run.
Brothers, run.
Run.
The timing is perfect.
Second Prince,
you have absorbed the Spiritual Power
of half the Mini Realm Scroll.
Ready to test your strength?
Time to turn the tide and make a name.
Your Highness,
show your power.
Bring them to heel.
Make them your first followers.
I am Ao Yi, destined to be a light
that shines upon the entire East Sea.
Senior.
I will save you.
Transform into a dragon.
Run. Keep up.
Run.
What is that?
A great Deity.
A Deity.
We are saved.
No dragon. Just a worm.
Run that way.
Don't go.
Give me a chance.
Dragon's Prophecy...
Still hasn't recovered.
What do we do now?
Seems we need the old way.
The old way?
Run.
Keep up.
Hurry. Run faster.
So impressive.
You absorbed half the scroll's power.
Even without transforming, you are still strong.
My power
is back.
Isn't he...
The worm from earlier?
No wonder he looks familiar.
Sea Deity Sect disciples.
Forgot what Sea Deity taught you?
Taught us what?
On my command.
Fire.
Cultivators of Seizing Sect.
Why commit such bloodshed?
Detached Master,
why do you think we came to your sect?
With your current cultivation,
you must foresee Ascendance Sect's
tribulation in 500 years.
How do you know that?
But when that tribulation arrives,
and we face life or death,
I believe the Three Sects here
can put aside the past
and stand as one.
I want to use that tribulation
to begin Unity of the Three Sects.
You were worried
your sect couldn't survive alone,
so you kept us as a backup plan.
But you didn't know
our Seizing Sect is your tribulation.
We came here today
to bury Ascendance Sect
along with your dream of unity.
Grandlord.
Attack!
Jiu Jiu is here. Meet your Death!
♪ Always a lamp to light the valley ♪
♪ Or flying up to the heavens alone ♪
♪ To demand justice for the world ♪
Backup?
Little Uncle.
Charge!
♪ Someone will answer for me ♪
Senior.
Thank goodness you're okay.
Where is Mentor?
He got blown away.
♪ Taking our steps together ♪
♪ Fearing no storm or karma ♪
Grandlord.
♪ Acting like fierce demons ♪
What's wrong, Grandlord?
♪ Who plots and schemes ♪
♪ And set formations in the world ♪
♪ I will go in and stir things up ♪
Why isn't Senior back yet?
♪ Amid the clamoring voices ♪
Senior.
Senior. I'm so glad you're okay.
Saw the fight outside and still ran out?
Copy Scripture of Steadiness 500 times.
I will.
Jiu Jiu.
Grandlord.
Why are you here?
Over a dozen miles away,
a Demon Army is heading this way.
Did Seizing Sect collude with them
to conquer Ascendance Sect?
Time to show them what we've got.
Disciples, after them.
Capture them all!
Here.
Where to?
- Grandlord.
Defending Formation.
Open.
Elders of all divisions, hold it firmly.
- Grandlord.
Grandlord.
What a pity.
We couldn't capture Zhao Gongming.
If we could make him the leader,
the story of Seizing Sect's attack
would be much more interesting.
Defending Formation?
Smash it.
Go. Go.
Disciples below Verity Immortal,
shelter in the Hall of Mortal Coils.
Careful.
Go, go, go.
Senior, should we run?
Have you reached Verity Immortal?
Not yet.
Then why are you just watching?
Run.
Keep up. Be careful.
Now that
the Grandlord is heavily injured,
I am the only Aureate Immortal here.
Naturally, I should give the orders.
With the Grandlord absent,
all orders
must be decided by the elders.
This is our sect's tradition.
Kuai Si,
do you want to break the rule?
There's no time to debate in crisis.
Do as I say.
All elders, lead the disciples
to retreat to Hall of Mortal Coils.
The Grandlord ordered before passing out
that we must hold the Defending Formation.
We should stay here
and feed it Spiritual Power.
Defend, and Spiritual Power runs dry.
Once the formation falls,
and we have no power left,
wouldn't that be suicide?
But the Grandlord said...
The Grandlord?
The Seizing Sect broke in
because the Grandlord messed up.
He let them into Ascendance Sect.
You...
That's true.
Our sect has been in total chaos
because the Grandlord allowed it.
The Elucidating guests fled the crisis.
And the Seizing disciples had schemes.
There is absolutely no honor
among these Three Sects.
You all...
He's right.
Please, Elders,
retreat to Hall of Mortal Coils now.
Do not delay.
Yes.
Wait.
If Seizing Sect and Demon Army attack,
what about the other divisions?
Then those divisions can only blame
their ill fortune.
Move aside.
Make way. All of you.
Move.
Grandlord.
This is bad.
Where are you going?
I'm looking for Mentor.
I don't know how he is.
You think I made no plans?
Wanna copy scriptures again?
All this noise.
What's going on?
Changshou, let me out.
Grandlord.
I failed you.
If I had patrolled carefully
and reported earlier,
maybe this wouldn't have happened.
Senior.
Take good care of Grandlord.
What are you doing?
I'm going out to strike down all I can.
I must avenge Grandlord.
Have you lost your mind?
I don't care.
Ever since I joined this sect,
I've done nothing but drink,
mess up, and cause trouble.
What else am I good for?
Even if you die,
would that make it right with Grandlord?
Then let this be Grand lord's punishment.
I'll pay with my life.
Out of my way.
Grandlord punished you, not for death.
He wants you alive.
So you can protect everyone.
If you hadn't patrolled today,
who would have saved us?
Every time Grandlord punished you,
others thought he was disappointed.
But he always favored you the most.
If Grandlord really hated you,
he'd have struck you.
But over all these years,
did he ever hurt you?
Jiu Jiu,
in the name of Senior,
I punish you on Grand lord's behalf.
Jiu Jiu of Griefbane, hear my command.
You must stay here
and protect the Hall of Mortal Coils
and all the disciples.
Do not take a single step away.
But I...
Obey the command.
I obey.
Senior.
Stop crying.
Mentor wasn't like this before.
Mentor
can definitely be saved.
Highly unlikely.
He's under Curse Sorcery.
Curse Sorcery?
What did I say?
Curse Sorcery.
A thousand years ago,
during the Deity-Demon War,
there was a demon clan
that could control minds with curses.
Later, that clan
was wiped out by the Grand Mage.
I guess some survived.
They're after the Seizing Sect.
Can my Mentor still be saved?
It's a long shot.
But for unresolved matters,
we must rely on our own efforts.
Thanks, Stone Man.
Senior.
Mentor will surely be back.
Ascendance Sect.
Let me out.
So noisy. Shut up.
Who are there?
You don't know who we are?
We are the Xiongs.
Born with divine strength and looks,
unmatched by anyone in the world.
In what way?
In being shameless?
Hey, Ascendance Sect.
Can you keep me here?
I come and go as I please.
I'm staying because I want to.
What took you so long?
Your Highness, I'm here to save you.
Your Highness?
Well...
It's just...
My family is a bit special.
You know each other?
Why did you pick on him yesterday?
Yesterday was a misunderstanding.
I didn't see he was holding back.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
Come here.
- She looks super rich.
- This battle is a human affair.
- It has nothing to do with us.
- We need a plan
to scam her.
Pearl Elites will protect you.
Good, let's get out of here first.
Come on.
Let's go.
What are we waiting for?
Stone Man.
Actually,
I
I can't leave with you.
Why?
Think about it.
My Mentor, Senior,
and my Juniors
are all here.
How can I abandon them?
An earthquake?
Don't worry.
Not a quake. The Defending Formation
is about to break.
We're doomed.
Set up the formation.
After today,
Ascendance Sect will be devastated.
Elder Kuai Si will save the day
and rebuild with West dawn's help.
From then on,
I'll shock the Primordial World
and make history.
The Ascendance Sect people
did gather on one peak.
Surround them and leave none alive.
We will kill Changgeng
and find the Pregenesis Sword.
You dare block my way?
A toad?
♪ I don't ask, too lazy to fight ♪
♪ I dare to live my own way ♪
♪ In the Primordial World ♪
♪ Who sings and drinks free ♪
♪ The stars smile at fireflies ♪
♪ Roaming the city with reckless courage ♪
Senior, what were you doing?
♪ And in dreams, I reign supreme ♪
Remember the Gnatsting Needle?
I read many books
until I found it
in one that recorded
about ancient demons.
It's called Gnatsting Needle.
A weapon of the Blood Gnat Clan.
The weapon Yuan Qing used to strike.
Right.
Since then,
I've been setting up defenses.
Didn't you notice
the local plants and animals
have been growing so fast?
♪ Let the thoughts weigh ♪
Senior, you are amazing.
You even kept a backup plan.
♪ Unruly ♪
♪ A carefree smile ♪
My linked maze formation
was upgraded and optimized
step by step
during their trials.
Now, it's a giant formation.
Even Zhao Gongming can't escape it,
let alone those attackers.
They don't stand a chance.
So you had it planned all along.
[Lost?]
What's wrong with this sect?
I have waited so long.
Why aren't they here?
Did they
run into trouble on the way?
Finally.
What is going on?
Elder Kuai Si,
Changgeng blocked our army.
Help us...
Mentor.
We waited for two hours,
and only a mosquito showed up.
Good.
Well done.
Keep patrolling.
Yes, Mentor.
If there is a flaw in your plan,
it must be your Mentor.
Relax, Yunxiao.
I put Mentor
in the absolute safest place
in our entire sect,
protected by a linked maze.
Aren't you afraid he'll break the art himself?
His foundation was damaged early on.
I treated him for thirty years.
If he forces through it,
it will ruin his foundation again.
When the next tribulation comes,
he will surely die.
Though Mentor isn't very bright,
he still values his life.
The unexpected always happens.
Aren't you worried you missed something?
After all, Fate is unpredictable.
Junior?
Senior?
Is that you, Senior?
Junior?
Senior, is that you?
Junior, where are you?
I'm here.
Are you not here?
Senior.
I'm here.
Don't leave, Senior.
I've been waiting here, Senior.
I thought someone would wait here.
Senior.
Senior, don't leave.
Don't leave.
I've been waiting here for you.
So
I was overthinking?
I've been waiting here for you.
Mentor.
Mentor is trying to break it.
Junior, cover for me again.
Okay.
Something's wrong?
That old man hid something from me.
So you miscalculated.
My calculations were flawless.
He's just too foolish.
He walked into such an obvious trap.
Did you ever consider
that not everyone in this world
calculates everything like you?
Senior.
Senior, wait for me.
I'm here, Senior.
Senior.
Senior, where are you?
I've been waiting here, Senior.
Junior.
Senior.
Junior, I'm here.
Senior?
Tomorrow, you'll leave for the assembly.
I'm worried your power is too weak
to defeat the demons.
So I made an amulet for you.
Junior, I'm right here.
Junior.
This jade talisman
was left by Senior.
Kuai Si.
My Senior
gave this jade talisman to me.
It's a Voice-Transmitting Jade Talisman.
Found where the Divine-Demon.
Tribulation occurred.
Inside this talisman
are the words Senior Wan Jiangyu
left for you.
Kuai Si.
There is nothing.
I cast a Silencing Spell.
Kuai Si!
Kuai Si.
Kuai Si. Junior.
Please, I beg you.
I beg you.
I'll do whatever you want.
I'm even willing to die.
Please undo the spell.
I want to hear what Senior said.
I want to hear her voice.
Do you want to know
what she actually said to you?
Yes.
Yes. Yes.
Just let Li Changshou
enter the Mini Realm Scroll,
and I'll undo this Silencing Spell.
Fine!
Fine.
Fine. Kuai Si.
Hurry and undo it.
Please undo it now.
Please. I'm begging you.
Kuai Si.
Please undo it.
Kuai Si, I beg you.
Senior.
Wanna know where she actually went?
Let me tell you.
Kuai Si.
Senior.
What did you do to this talisman?
This talisman
was indeed left by Wan Jiangyu.
However,
I didn't find it in the South Sea.
It was in Kuru Land.
When I killed her.
Back then,
you were a perfect couple.
Envied by everyone.
But she was so beautiful,
you weren't the only one
who fell for her.
Junior.
Why?
Why did she love only you?
Only you, Qi Yuan.
Why wouldn't she even look at me?
Senior.
What makes you so special?
Why you? Why?
I thought if I ruined you,
she'd finally look at me.
But I never expected
she would leave Ascendance Sect
just to save you.
For a useless waste like you.
She went into danger in North Land.
Just for a waste like you!
I hated her for that.
So I followed her
all the way to North Land.
I lured a fierce beast
to attack her.
Senior, are you okay?
Kuai Si, why are you here?
Don't try to talk. I'll get you out.
Come on.
I won't make it.
There's something.
I'd like to ask you.
Please take this Jade Talisman
back to Ascendance Sect
and give it to Qi Yuan.
I have so much to tell him.
It's all in the Jade Talisman.
It's for Qi Yuan?
Please.
Give it to Qi Yuan.
Okay.
Senior.
I promise.
I'll surely give it to Qi Yuan.
All these years,
you've been waiting for her like a fool.
Actually,
she died at my hand long ago.
Qi Yuan.
Watching you suffer love sickness daily,
it just makes me happy.
Resentment
is the finest weapon in this world.
♪ See mortal joys and sorrows ♪
♪ Reunions and partings, as fate unfolds ♪
♪ Alas, love has many twists and turns ♪
♪ Memories filled with sorrow ♪
♪ Slowly, wishes turn to regret ♪
♪ You've gone afar, like mist fading ♪
♪ Tearfully, this life's bond is not over ♪
♪ Past fragments vanish into night ♪
♪ Down a few more cups of wine ♪
♪ Through land and sea, I ask you to come ♪
♪ For honor's sake, upright and grand ♪
♪ Alas, our story is short ♪
♪ Slowly, wishes turn to regret ♪
♪ You've gone afar, like mist fading ♪
♪ Tearfully, this life's bond is not over ♪
♪ Past fragments vanish into night ♪